<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.program.xxxstream" name="[COLOR darkred][I]KOBRA [/I][/COLOR][COLOR ghostwhite] XXX STREAM WIZARD[/COLOR]" version="1.0.1" provider-name="[COLOR darkred][I]KOBRA [/I][/COLOR]">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="startup.py" start="login" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">[COLOR darkred][I]KOBRA [/I][/COLOR][COLOR ghostwhite] XXX STREAM WIZARD[/COLOR]</summary>
    <description lang="en">You must be 18 or over to use this add_on. This program provides easy access to Kobra XXX Streams</description>
	<disclaimer lang="en">Kobra XXX Stream does not endorse any content provided by any linked sites, nor does it assume any responsibility for the interpretation or add-on of any information originating from such content. In addition, Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation. We are not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC foundation. All product names, logos, and brands are property of their respective owners. All company, product and service names used in this add-on are for identification purposes only. All add-ons provided are for educational use only and we take no responsability for any content viewed via these add-ons. Use of these names, logos, and brands does not imply endorsement. We do not accept responsibility for any loss or damage caused by the use of any material from this add-on. we recommend that users re-check all material with their own anti-virus software. You must be 18 or over to access this add-on! the materials available within this add-on include graphic visual depictions and descriptions of nudity and sexual activity. By using this add-on you agree to the following: 1. You are an adult, at least 18 years of age, you are familiar with and understand the standards and laws of your local community regarding sexually-oriented media. You represent that, based on your familiarity with the standards and laws of your local community, you will not be violating any applicable standards or laws by requesting, receiving, downloading or possessing any of the video, audio, graphics, images or text adult material available on this add-on. 2. You hereby acknowledge that any use of this add-on is at your sole risk. You understand that by accepting the terms of this agreement, you are agreeing to hold the publisher of this add-on harmless from any responsibilities or liabilities related to your use of this add-on and the adult material contained herein. 3. You will not permit any person(s) under 18 years of age to have access to any of the adult materials contained in this add-on. 4. You are voluntarily choosing to access this add-on, because you want to view, use, read or hear the various apps and adult materials that are available. Yuu agree to immediately exit from this add-on if you are in any way offended by the sexual nature of any adult material. 5. If you use this add-on in violation of these terms, or use this add-on where such use is illegal, you may be in violation of local and/or federal laws. You agree that you are solely responsible for your use of this add-on and any linked third party web sites, and agree to indemnify publisher against any claims arising out of such use. 6. By entering the add-on, you agree to abide by the complete terms and conditions of use of this add-on.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
